{"1": {"question": "Schubert: What is the instrumentation of the piece?", "correct": "Voice and piano", "incorrect": ["Solo instrument and piano", "Orchestra", "String quartet", "Two pianos"]}, "2": {"question": "Schubert: What does Frühlingstraum mean?", "correct": "Spring dream", "incorrect": ["Winter dream", "Fruity Plum", "Violin", "Autumn dream"]}, "3": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of song is it?", "correct": "An art song", "incorrect": ["A pop song", "hell nah", "A sing song sang sung", "An instrumental song"]}, "4": {"question": "Schubert: What is D. 911", "correct": "Catalogue of his works", "incorrect": ["A random letter followed by a number", "Doomsday, 911 incident", "His 911th work", "A magazine catalogue"]}, "5": {"question": "Schubert: Who wrote the text for the work?", "correct": "Wilhelm Müller", "incorrect": ["J.K. Rowling", "Marcus Hildebrandt", "Leo", "Morenz Bittermann"]}, "6": {"question": "Schubert: What does Lied mean in German?", "correct": "Song", "incorrect": ["Piece", "Music", "Piano", "Past tense for 'lie'"]}, "7": {"question": "Schubert: How many songs are in the set called Winterreise?", "correct": "24", "incorrect": ["11", "16", "4", "911"]}, "8": {"question": "Schubert: In which place is Frühlingstraum in the set called Winterreise?", "correct": "11th", "incorrect": ["12th", "24th", "2nd", "DNF"]}, "9": {"question": "Schubert: What does Lied mean as a musical genre designation?", "correct": "A song set to German text", "incorrect": ["A song set to Italian text", "A piece of music with words", "Words with a piece of music", "A piece with words of music"]}, "10": {"question": "Schubert: How far back in time do Lied go?", "correct": "The Middle Ages", "incorrect": ["Jesus times", "The Renaissance", "The Dark Ages", "Prehistoric times (e.g. dinosaur)"]}, "11": {"question": "Schubert: In what time period did Lied develop to widespread recognition?", "correct": "The nineteenth century", "incorrect": ["Jesus times", "The eighteenth century", "10 minutes", "The seventeenth century"]}, "12": {"question": "Schubert: The devleopment of the Lied into widespread recognition had its roots where?", "correct": "The second half of the eighteenth century", "incorrect": ["The first half of the eighteenth century", "In the ground", "The second half of the seventeenth century", "The first half of the nineteenth century"]}, "13": {"question": "Schubert: What are the main reasons for the development of Lied into widespread recognition?", "correct": "The growth of German as a literary language, and how language can help social cohesion", "incorrect": ["The growth of Nazi Germany and Hitler's mo", "The growth of German as a literary language, and the development of Germany into a first-world nation", "The spread of European music across the world, and how language can help social cohesion", "Food from Germany becoming more popular around the world, and the love of their toilets"]}, "14": {"question": "Schubert: Who was at the forefront of the development of Lied into widespread recognition?", "correct": "Johann Wolfang von Goethe", "incorrect": ["Johann Sebastian Bach", "Heinrich Mitter", "Elmar Preiszner", "Ralf Reiter"]}, "15": {"question": "Schubert: What idea was developed by Johann Gottfried Herder?", "correct": "Language is the most powerful determinant of social cohesion", "incorrect": ["Music is the most powerful determinant of social cohesion", "The reason for the combination of music and language is that it sounds good", "That German food is tasty", "Language is the key tool of communication within a society"]}, "16": {"question": "What happened to Joe mama?", "correct": "They changed their last name to papa", "incorrect": ["They changed their last name to Biden", "Died in a hole R.I.P.", "Stopped practising saxophone so got spanked", "Joe"]}, "17": {"question": "Schubert: Whyy were peasants interested in Lied?", "correct": "The idea that Lied united everyone into one class", "incorrect": ["Lied gave them an opportunity to become rich performing it", "Lied let them understand what it was like to be in the upper class", "Peasants had a natural musical aptitude and therefore found it easier to learn and play", "They had nothing else to do"]}, "18": {"question": "Hello", "correct": "Goodbye", "incorrect": ["Die", "Why", "Hi", "Sigh"]}, "19": {"question": "Schubert: Why was much of the German poetry written in the early stages try to disconnect from the sophistication of the town/city?", "correct": "Town dominated by Italian opera, didn't want that style of music", "incorrect": ["Town dominated by Italian opera so they tried to rip it off outside of town", "The town was dominated by French opera, didn't want that style of music", "Town was dominated by German opera, but they didn't want that genre of music", "The sophistication of the urbanised areas did not suit the lifestyle of the peasants"]}, "20": {"question": "Schubert: The striving of German poetry during late 18th to early 19th Centuries toward oral folk traditions was for what purpose?", "correct": "People wanted an art that was unmediated by artificial formal conventions", "incorrect": ["People wanted music that had no connection to the music of the wealthy", "To revive folk music as it was very popular when it was around", "To remember and respect the ancestors of their music", "People wanted an art form that was not influenced by wealth or power"]}, "21": {"question": "Schubert: The urges for an art that was unmediated by artificial conventions (e.g. Italian opera) was amplified by what?", "correct": "The emerging Romantic movement", "incorrect": ["The emerging classical movement", "The emerging jazz movement", "Donald Trump's unwillingness to back down", "The emerging renaissance movement"]}, "22": {"question": "Schubert: What did the emerging Romantic movement emphasise?", "correct": "Unfettered expressions of feeling and emotion rather than the abstract appreciation of form", "incorrect": ["Undisturbed expressions of abstract appreciation of form rather than those of feeling and emotion", "The serious lack of aid provided by developed countries to developing countries", "Expressive techniques that were unique to the Romantic movement", "The emerging Romantic composers"]}, "23": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of feeling could this kind of music inspire in the individual?", "correct": "Feelings of the power of nature and awe and wonder", "incorrect": ["Feelings of the power of nature and resentment towards it", "Feelings of the weakness of nature and its dependence on humankind", "The awe and wonder inspired by a burrito", "How bad BTS is at making music (jk they don't make music)"]}, "24": {"question": "Schubert: What effect did the growing availability and popularity of the piano have on the development of the Romantic Lied?", "correct": "Led to the increasing numbers of German Lied being produced, due to presence in peoples' homes", "incorrect": ["Led to a serious shortage of piano teachers", "Led to a boom in the musical instrument manufacturing industry", "Led to the increasing numbers of German Lied being produced due to the lack of piano teachers", "Led to increasing numbers of home insurance claims due to the increased presence of pianos in peoples' homes"]}, "25": {"question": "Schubert: What caused composers to elevate the piano's role to support the text in Lied?", "correct": "The capacity for the piano to provide a level of inflection and subtlety not achievable on harpsichord", "incorrect": ["The capacity for the harpsichord to provide a level of inflection and subtelty not achievable on a piano", "The ability of the piano to play a variety of note durations and dynamics not achievable on a harpsichord", "The way the piano is able to play in a much larger range not achievable on harpsichord", "The ability to open the lid of the piano which is a cool function"]}, "26": {"question": "Schubert: Who was the first composer to realise the potential for a fusion of German poetic setting and sophisticated accompaniment", "correct": "Schubert", "incorrect": ["Mozart", "Bach", "Finzi", "Xi Jinping"]}, "27": {"question": "Schubert: How many Lieder did Schubert compose in his career?", "correct": "Over 600", "incorrect": ["Over 800", "Under 100", "Under 600", "Over 1000"]}, "28": {"question": "Schubert: How are song cycles unified?", "correct": "All the songs are composed by the same composer, words from same poet, and have references to a particular theme or tell the same story", "incorrect": ["All the songs were composed by the same composer but the words were from different poets, and the dynamics were the same", "The songs were composed by different composers and the words are composed by different poets, and the story is different", "A binder, maybe some paper clips or staples", "By recurring motifs and ideas, also by using the same modes/keys"]}, "29": {"question": "Schubert: Who was the first composer to link individual Lieder together into unified collections?`", "correct": "Beethoven", "incorrect": ["Mozart", "Finzi", "Schubert", "Xi Jinping"]}, "30": {"question": "Schubert: What was Beethoven's first song cycle?", "correct": "An die ferne Geliebte Op. 98", "incorrect": ["Seufzer eines Ungeliebten - Gegenliebe WoO 118", "Liederkreis, Op. 39", "Dichterliebe", "The Dark Side of the Moon, Op. Pink Floyd"]}, "31": {"question": "Schubert: How many different approaches to a song cycle emerged?", "correct": "Two", "incorrect": ["Three", "Four", "One", "Ten"]}, "32": {"question": "Schubert: What was Beethoven's approach to song-cycles?", "correct": "Link the songs  by explicit recollection of musical motives between certain of the individual numbers", "incorrect": ["Link the songs by using a consistent range of dynamics and expressive techniques throughout the songs", "Link the songs through the use of musical ideas that remained the same throughout every song", "Present the songs as musically independent numbers and allow the narrative relationship to be more implicit", "Link the songs as musically reliant variables on the dominant seventh dimished chord of the tonic mode major key"]}, "33": {"question": "Schubert: What was the non-Beethoven approach to song-cycles?", "correct": "Present the songs as musically indepenedent numbers and to allow the narrative relationship to be more implicit", "incorrect": ["Link the songs by explicit recollection of musical motifs between certain of the individual numbers", "Link the songs through the use of musical ideas that remained the same throughout every song", "Present the songs as musically dependent numbers and allow the narrative relationship to be more implicit", "Link the songs as musically reliant variables on the dominant seventh dimished chord of the tonic mode major key"]}, "34": {"question": "Schubert: Which approach to song cycles was favoured by Schubert?", "correct": "The non-Beethoven one", "incorrect": ["The Beethoven one", "Both of them, because Franz likes variety", "Neither, because he brought about a third style that was his own and more obscure", "The Mozart one"]}, "35": {"question": "Schubert: When was Winterreise composed?", "correct": "1828", "incorrect": ["1928", "1826", "1905", "2020"]}, "36": {"question": "Schubert: Did Wilhelm Müller consider the poems as a cycle?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Probably", "Why not"]}, "37": {"question": "Schubert: In which perspective is the poem told from?", "correct": "First person", "incorrect": ["Second person", "Third person", "Fourth person", "Patient zero"]}, "38": {"question": "Schubert: How is the poet introduced in the set of poems?", "correct": "Leaving a village, passing the gate of his lost love he won in spring but has now lost", "incorrect": ["Leaving a village, passing the bakery at which he always used to buy bread from", "Entering a village, passing the gate of his lost love he won in spring but has not lost", "Leaving a village, passing his home where many memories were created", "Entering a village, smelling the delicious smells of baked bread and the pretty sights"]}, "39": {"question": "Schubert: In which sense is the poet on a journey?", "correct": "Physical and psychological", "incorrect": ["Physical and spiritual", "Spiritual and psychological", "Environmental and psychological", "Biological and psychological"]}, "40": {"question": "Schubert: What is an idea in the text that Müller constantly returns to?", "correct": "Constrast between illusion and reality", "incorrect": ["Contrast between Spring and Winter", "Contrast between walking and sitting", "Contrast between dreams and nightmares", "Contast between love and loneliness"]}, "41": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of attitude does the poet have?", "correct": "He is an outcast who will wander in solitude and never know companionship", "incorrect": ["He is highly likeable and will always have the companionship and love from others", "He is an outcast who will wander in companionship and love", "He is an extrovert who will wander in solitude and never know companionship", "He is an outcast who has many friends and his highly likebale"]}, "42": {"question": "Schubert: How is the higher awareness on the part of the poet expressed?", "correct": "He refers to the dreams of others and he knows the cold reality that awaits everyone", "incorrect": ["He refers to the dreams of higher beings and knows the cold reality that awaits everyone", "He refers to the dreams of others and he knows the pleasant reality that awaits everyone", "He refers to his own dreams and can see the future that awaits everyone", "The poet is able to see the cold reality that awaits everyone through his own dreams"]}, "43": {"question": "Schubert: What kind of rhyme scheme does Frühlingstraum have?", "correct": "abcabc", "incorrect": ["aabaac", "ababab", "abcdab", "aabbabababaaabbabababbabababbaababbabababababbababbab"]}, "44": {"question": "Schubert: What is the poet trying to promote in the text?", "correct": "A folk-like simplicity and artlessness", "incorrect": ["A folk-like complexity and artfulness", "The simplicity of the text", "A city-like complexity and thoughtfulness", "A city-like simpleness and artlessness"]}, "45": {"question": "Schubert: In some songs in the set Winterreise, the poet dreams himself, and awakens to a harsh reality. Is this the case in Frühlingstraum?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["Maybe", "I don't know, you tell me", "Most likely", "It is possible"]}, "46": {"question": "Schubert: How many quatrains does Frühlingstraum contain?", "correct": "6", "incorrect": ["8", "4", "2", "1"]}, "47": {"question": "Schubert: Each line in the poem comprises a loose what?", "correct": "Iambic trimeter", "incorrect": ["Iambic pentameter", "Grip on reality", "Iambic dimeter", "Iambic tetrameter"]}, "48": {"question": "Schubert: How can the poetic meter throughout the poem be described?", "correct": "Simple and consistent", "incorrect": ["Complex and irregular", "Complex and unpredictable", "Simple yet unpredictable", "Complex and consistent"]}, "49": {"question": "Schubert: How are the lines grouped?", "correct": "In pairs", "incorrect": ["In threes", "In fours", "In groups of ten thouSAND MILLION BILLION TRILLION GAZILLION", "Individually"]}, "50": {"question": "Schubert: How many metric feet are there in each line?", "correct": "Three", "incorrect": ["Two", "Four", "Seventeen", "Eleven thousand, nine hundred and eighty-four point three"]}, "51": {"question": "Schubert: What do the metric feet in most cases consist of?", "correct": "iambs (unstressed-stressed)", "incorrect": ["amphibrach (unstressed-stressed-unstressed)", "pyrrhic (unstressed-unstressed)", "dactyl (stressed-unstressed-unstressed)", "anapest (unstressed-unstressed-stressed)"]}, "52": {"question": "Schubert: In the first line of each pair, the final foot is what?", "correct": "amphibrach (unstressed-stressed-unstressed)", "incorrect": ["iambs (unstressed-stressed)", "pyrrhic (unstressed-unstressed)", "dactyl (stressed-unstressed-unstressed)", "anapest (unstressed-unstressed-stressed)"]}, "53": {"question": "What renders the metre loose rather than strict?", "correct": "Short additional syllables", "incorrect": ["Long additional syllables", "Medium-lenght additional syllables", "A shortage of syllables in some places", "A surplus of unnecessary syllables"]}, "54": {"question": "Schubert: Does the two-line metric preocess apply throughout the entire verse?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Probably NOT", "Huh"]}, "55": {"question": "Schubert: What are melismas?", "correct": "A group of notes sung to one syllable", "incorrect": ["A group of syllables placed on one note", "A group of notes sung on a group of syllables", "A group of notes sung on two syllables", "A syllable sung on a note"]}, "56": {"question": "Schubert: What does syllabic mean?", "correct": "One syllable per note", "incorrect": ["Two sylllables per note", "Three syllables per note", "Two notes per syllable", "One syllable per three notes"]}, "57": {"question": "Schubert: What do the quatrains marked A (1 and 4) symbolise?", "correct": "Spring, birds and flowers, blossoming love", "incorrect": ["A quatrain", "Cold reality of WInter, harsh calls of birds", "Yearning to return to dream state, despair that is all illusion", "The harsh reality of the seasonal cycle"]}, "58": {"question": "Schubert: What do the quatrains marked B (2 and 5) symbolise?", "correct": "Cold reality of Winter, harsh calls of birds", "incorrect": ["Spring, birds and flowers, blossoming love", "A quatrain", "Yearning to return to dream state, despair that is all illusion", "The harsh reality of the seasonal cycle"]}, "59": {"question": "Schubert: What do the quatrains marked C (3 and 6) symbolise?", "correct": "Yearning to return to dream state, despair that all is illusion", "incorrect": ["Spring, birds and flowers, blossoming love", "Cold reality of Winter, harsh calls of birds", "A quatrain", "The harsh reality of the seasonal cycle"]}, "60": {"question": "Schubert: How many times does the poem cycle through the dream-reality-longing (ABC)?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["3", "1", "4", "So many times you're gonna lose count :)"]}, "61": {"question": "Schubert: What bars is Section A?", "correct": "1-14", "incorrect": ["15-26", "2-15", "26-44", "1-16"]}, "62": {"question": "Schubert: What bars is Section B?", "correct": "15-26", "incorrect": ["13-25", "44-43", "15-28", "1-14"]}, "63": {"question": "Schubert: What bars is Section C?", "correct": "27-44", "incorrect": ["15-26", "1-14", "25-44", "27-45"]}, "64": {"question": "Schubert: How does Schubert delineate the contrasts between the different sections?", "correct": "Changes of key/mode, tempo, style, metre", "incorrect": ["Changes of key/mode, dynamics, style, texture", "Change of dynamics and tempo but not expressive techniques", "Expressive techniques, dynamics, key/mode, tempo", "Style, mode, metre, dynamics"]}, "65": {"question": "Schubert: What do major modes represent in this song?", "correct": "Dreaming, spring, warmth, love", "incorrect": ["Reality, winter, coldness, loneliness", "Reality, summer, heat, companionship", "Dreaming, winter, warmth, loneliness", "Spring, coldness, loneliness, love"]}, "66": {"question": "Schubert: What do minor modes represent in this song?", "correct": "Reality, winter, coldness, loneliness", "incorrect": ["Dreaming, spring, warmth, love", "Reality, summer, heat, companionship", "Dreaming, winter, warmth, loneliness", "Spring, coldness, loneliness, love"]}, "67": {"question": "Schubert: Which section comes closest to adopting a direct, folk song-like style?", "correct": "Section A", "incorrect": ["Section B", "Section C ", "Section D", "Sections A and B"]}, "68": {"question": "Schubert: The material in section A is almost entirely...", "correct": "Diatonic", "incorrect": ["Chromatic", "Minor", "Gone", "Changed"]}, "69": {"question": "Schubert: The material in section A is cast in how many simple phrases?", "correct": "2", "incorrect": ["4", "6", "8", "1"]}, "70": {"question": "Schubert: What does etwas bewegt mean?", "correct": "With some movement", "incorrect": ["tgeweb sawte", "With patience", "With movement", "Slightly faster"]}, "71": {"question": "Schubert: How does the piano accompaniment foreshadow the singer's line in Section A?", "correct": "A brief four-bar introduction", "incorrect": ["A brief two-bar introduction", "A brief one-bar introduction", "A brief six-bar introduction", "A brief eighteen-bar introduction"]}, "72": {"question": "Schubert: What is siciliana?", "correct": "A slow musical style with lilting rhythms resembling a slow jig", "incorrect": ["A type of pizza", "A fast musical style with syncopated rhythms resembling a rondo", "A slow musical style with even rhythms resembling a waltz", "A fast musical style that has irregular rhythms resembling a six year old learning the piano"]}, "73": {"question": "Schubert: What kinds of themes are siciliana rhythms usually associated with?", "correct": "Nature and simple bucolic life", "incorrect": ["Buildings and complicated city life", "Nature and complex bucolic life", "Margherita, meat lovers, Hawaiian, pepperoni", "Simple country life and farms with cows"]}, "74": {"question": "Schubert: Where can a simple period be detected in Section A?", "correct": "Antecedent (bars 5-8) and consequent (bars 9-14)", "incorrect": ["Consequent (bars 5-8) and antecedent (bars 9-14)", "From bars 4-15", "Antecedent (bars 9-14) and consequent (bars 15-21)", "Antecedent (bars 6-9) and consequent (bars 10-15)"]}, "75": {"question": "Schubert: How does Section B contrast to Section A?", "correct": "Tempo increase, key change, mode becomes minor, accompaniment more staccato", "incorrect": ["Key change, mode becomes major, accompaniment more legato, tempo decrease", "Tempo increase, key change, mode becomes major, accompaniment more staccato", "Tempo decrase, key change, mode becomes minor, accompaniment more legato", "Tempo increase, key change, key becomes minor, accompaniment more staccato"]}, "76": {"question": "Schubert: What is sustained in the piano part by a tonic pedal in section B?", "correct": "A low tremolo", "incorrect": ["A high tremolo", "Basso continuo", "Slash chords", "An inappropriate accomapniment"]}, "77": {"question": "Schubert: What do the triplet figures marked x in section B act as?", "correct": "Jolts that destablise dream equilibrium", "incorrect": ["Jolts that reinforce the dream equilibrium", "Jolts that make the listener pee their pants", "Jolts that destablise the Winter reality", "Lead-ins to the next bars"]}, "78": {"question": "Schubert: What does schnell mean?", "correct": "Fast", "incorrect": ["Slow", "Walking", "Medium", "Speeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeed"]}, "79": {"question": "Schubert: What are augmented 6th chords?", "correct": "Chromatic chords which resolve to the dominant or sometimes the tonic", "incorrect": ["Chromatic chords which resolve to the tonic or sometimes the dominant", "The 6th is augmented (duh)", "Diatonic chords which resolve to the dominant or sometimes the tonic", "Diatonic chords which resolve to the tonic or sometimes the dominant"]}, "80": {"question": "Schubert: How are augmented 6th chords constructed?", "correct": "On the minor 6th degree of the scale and always include a note an augmented 6th above that", "incorrect": ["On the major 6th degree of the scale and always include a note an augmented 6th above that", "Intervals of minor 6ths piled on top of each other", "On the minor 6th degree of the scale and always include a note an augmented 2nd above that", "On the major 6th degree of hte scale and always include a note an augmented 2nd above that"]}, "81": {"question": "Schubert: The triplet figures marked x in section B involve inversions of what chord?", "correct": "The French augmented 6th chord", "incorrect": ["The German augmented 6th chord", "The Italian augmented 6th chord", "The French augmented 2nd chord", "The French suspended 6th chord"]}, "82": {"question": "Schubert: What is the Neopolitan 6th in bar 23?", "correct": "A supertonic triad constrcuted on the lowered 2nd degree", "incorrect": ["A supertonic triad constructed on the lowered 6th degree", "A supertonic triad constructed on the 5th degree", "A supertonic fourth constructed on the 5th degree of the 6th mode of the dominant 7th chord", "The 6th flavour of Neopolitan ice-cream"]}, "83": {"question": "Schubert: Does chromatic writing continue over the tonic pedal in bars 22-26?", "correct": "Yes", "incorrect": ["No", "Maybe", "Possibly", "Probably"]}, "84": {"question": "Schubert: What feeling is created by the rapid modulation, chromatic harmony, minor-mode colouring and angular accompaniment in Section B?", "correct": "A powerful sense of disturbance, disorientation and distress - waking up from a dream", "incorrect": ["A powerful sense of reassurance, sleepiness and calmness - like falling asleep", "A powerful sense of disturbance, disorientation and distress - playing a note during a rest in an orchestra", "A powerful sense of disturbance, disorientation and distress - waking up from a dreamless sleep", "A powerful sense of reassurance, sleepiness and calmness - like eating chocolate"]}, "85": {"question": "Schubert: What does langsam mean?", "correct": "Slow", "incorrect": ["Fast", "Medium", "Turtle", "Speeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeed"]}, "86": {"question": "Schubert: What meter does Section C introduce?", "correct": "Simple duple", "incorrect": ["Simple triple", "Simple quadruple", "Compound duple", "Compound triple"]}, "87": {"question": "Schubert: What helps to set up a sense of stillness in section C after the agitation from section B?", "correct": "A new accompaniment pattern that remains quite constant", "incorrect": ["A new accompaniment pattern that varies a lot", "A reused accompaniment pattern that remains quite constant", "A new accompaniment that is constant in some parts and different in others", "An old accompaniment pattern that was drawn from a different song"]}, "88": {"question": "Schubert: The first two lines of text in Section C appear with a return to what key?", "correct": "The tonic major", "incorrect": ["The tonic minor", "The relative minor", "The dominant major", "The subdominant major"]}, "89": {"question": "Schubert: The first two lines in Section C are repeated, but what happens to the expected strong perfect cadence at bar 36?", "correct": "It is withheld", "incorrect": ["It is played as expected", "It is played and then repeated", "It is withheld and played two bars later", "It is played as unexpected, because they read the sheet music upside down"]}, "90": {"question": "Schubert: The arrival of the tonic in the bass is delayed until the final cadence in Section C, but what has changed regarding the mode?", "correct": "The mode is now minor", "incorrect": ["The mode is now major", "The mode is now diminished", "The mode is now dominant7", "The mode is now dark mode (iOS 14 feature)"]}, "91": {"question": "Schubert: How can the closure of Section C be described?", "correct": "Soaked with a feeling of loss and despair", "incorrect": ["Soaked with maple syrup like a pancake", "Soaked with a feeling of happiness and completion", "Soaked with a feeling of resentment and anger", "Epic"]}}